http://www.pacivilwar.com/privacy.html

Look for your ancestors in this PA genealogy database of American Civil War soldiers
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
Pennsylvania Volunteers of the Civil War
This Web site does not have pop-ups
This Web site does have pop-up advertisements.
If you are receiving pop-up ads when you visit this site, the ads are probably coming from spyware that was downloaded and installed on your computer without your permission from another site.
To delete this unwanted spyware from your computer, download the FREE spyware remover from Microsoft.
Microsoft Anti-Spyware
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
Pennsylvania Volunteers of the Civil War
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Special Relationships
Some of the advertisements may contain cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs, deliver viruses to your computer, or deliver e-mail spam. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
Cookies received with banner ads may be collected by the ad company to record the number of times an advertisement was shown.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you register at a site, or if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Pennsylvania Volunteers of the Civil War
Search original documents on Fold3
Ancestry.com Civil War Databases
U.S. Civil War Soldiers
6.3 million soldiers who served in the American Civil War.
Special Veterans' 1890 Census
Lists the veteran's name or widow's name, rank, year of enlistment, and year of discharge.
Civil War POWs
Confederate and Union Civil War Prisoners of War
PA Veteran Burials Records
Index cards of burial records of Pennsylvania veterans 1777 - 1999 including the Civil War.
Want to find out if your ancestor was a Civil War soldier?
Follow these research ideas.
Want to Help?
Copyright ©
Pennsylvania Civil War Volunteers
1997-2015 All rights reserved.
